A Finding Aid to the Lee Nordness business records and papers, circa 1931-1992 (bulk 1954-1984), in the Archives of American Art AAA.nordlee
Archives of American Art
- Lee Nordness Galleries Exhibition Section, Inc., 1938-1985; Series 2; 25.4 Linear feet Boxes 68-93, 120
  - Correspondence, 1961-1984; 2.1
    - "G" Miscellaneous, 1968-1981 (Box 68, Folder 40-41)
    - Galleries, 1964-1976 (Box 68, Folder 42-43)
    - Grosso Moving and Packing Co., 1969-1971 (Box 68, Folder 44)
    - Group Show Price Lists, 1966-circa 1968 (Box 68, Folder 45)
    - "H" Miscellaneous, 1968-1984 (Box 68, Folder 46-47)
    - Harmon Gallery, 1964-1976 (Box 68, Folder 48-49)
    - Hughley, George, circa 1968-1974 (Box 68, Folder 50)
    - "I" Miscellaneous, 1968-1969 (Box 69, Folder 1)
    - Installment Buyers (Paid in Full), 1966 (Box 69, Folder 2)
    - Insurance, John Lennon, 1981 (Box 69, Folder 3)
    - Insurance Claims Closed, 1968-1973 (Box 69, Folder 4)
    - Interior Design, 1968 (Box 69, Folder 5)
    - "J" Miscellaneous, 1968-1970 (Box 69, Folder 6)
    - Job Applicants, 1968 (Box 69, Folder 7)
    - Jurying, 1971-1974 (Box 69, Folder 8)
    - "K" Miscellaneous, 1968-1980 (Box 69, Folder 9-10)
    - Kelly [Misc. Consignment Sheets], 1969-1981 (Box 69, Folder 11)
    - Krannert Art Museum, University of Illinois, 1968-1969 (Box 69, Folder 12)
    - "L" Miscellaneous, 1968-1979 (Box 69, Folder 13-14)
    - Lancaster, Edward, circa 1960s-1975 (Box 69, Folder 15)
    - Lennon, John, "Bag One" Correspondence, 1969-1970 (Box 69, Folder 16)
    - Lennon, John, "Bag One" Exhibition Correspondence, 1970-1973 (Box 69, Folder 17)
    - Lightolier, 1968 (Box 69, Folder 18)
    - Loan Form, 1965-1967 (Box 69, Folder 19)
    - "M" Miscellaneous, 1967-1984 (Box 69, Folder 20-21)
    - Magazine Subscriptions, Book and Catalog Orders, 1970; 1968 (Box 69, Folder 22)
    - Mailing List, Oriental, circa 1968-1974 (Box 69, Folder 23)
    - "Man and His World," Shows Out of Gallery, 1969 (Box 69, Folder 24)
    - Metromedia, 1968-1974 (Box 69, Folder 25)
    - Miami Art Center, 1969-1970 (Box 69, Folder 26)
    - Mickelson Gallery, 1968-1969 (Box 69, Folder 27)
    - Morgan Manhattan Storage, 1973-1975 (Box 69, Folder 28)
    - Museum Shows, 1967 (Box 69, Folder 29)
    - Museums, 1968-1979 (Box 69, Folder 30-32)
    - "N" Miscellaneous, 1968-1979 (Box 69, Folder 33-34)
    - National Academy of Design, 1984 (Box 69, Folder 35)
    - NAACP Exhibition ["1969: 12 Afro-American Artists"], 1968-1974 (Box 69, Folder 36-38)
    - NAACP Exhibition Catalog ["1969: 12 Afro-American Artists"] (Box 69, Folder 39)
    - New Chinese Painting Show Hong Kong, 1971 (Box 69, Folder 40)
    - New Painters, 1975 (Box 69, Folder 41)
    - New Sculptors, 1975 (Box 69, Folder 42)
    - No-Nos, 1969-1974 (Box 69, Folder 43)
    - No Nos No Nos, 1976 (Box 69, Folder 44)
    - Nordness, Lee, On Vacation, 1973 (Box 69, Folder 45)
    - "O" Miscellaneous, 1969-1979 (Box 69, Folder 46-47)
    - Objects:USA, 1969 (Box 69, Folder 48)
    - Overs, Gail, The Cedar Gallery, Ltd., 1972 (Box 69, Folder 49)
    - "P" Miscellaneous, 1965-1975 (Box 69, Folder 50-51)
    - "P" Miscellaneous, 1977-1980 (Box 70, Folder 1)
    - Pan American and Desa, 1973-1974 (Box 70, Folder 2)
    - Permissions, 1977-1979 (Box 70, Folder 3)
    - Personnel, circa 1968-1969 (Box 70, Folder 4-5)
    - Photographers, 1975, undated (Box 70, Folder 6)
    - Press Releases, circa 1968-1974 (Box 70, Folder 7)
    - Publicity, 1969-1970 (Box 70, Folder 8-9)
    - "Q" Miscellaneous, 1982 (Box 70, Folder 10)
    - Quinlan Gallery, 1969 (Box 70, Folder 11)
    - Captain's Gallery (Bud Quinn), 1975-1976 (Box 70, Folder 12)
    - "R" Miscellaneous, 1968-1979 (Box 70, Folder 13-14)
    - Receipts (Purchased Works), 1968 (Box 70, Folder 15)
    - Returned Mail, Artists, 1974 (Box 70, Folder 16)
    - "S" Miscellaneous, 1968-1983 (Box 70, Folder 17-18)
    - Saginaw Art Museum, 1968-1970 (Box 70, Folder 19)
    - Shipping Receipts, 1968-1971 (Box 70, Folder 20)
    - Shows Out of Gallery, 1968-1970 (Box 70, Folder 21)
    - Shows Out of Gallery, In Preparation, 1967-1968 (Box 70, Folder 22)
    - Shows Touring, 1971-1972 (Box 70, Folder 23)
    - Smithsonian Institution, "12 Afro-American Artists", 1968-1972 (Box 70, Folder 24)
    - Sunami, Soichi, Photographer, 1967-1968 (Box 70, Folder 25)
    - Springs Mills, 1967-1968 (Box 70, Folder 26)
    - Starr, Mr., 1981 (Box 70, Folder 27)
    - Stassen Kostos and Mason, 1973-1974 (Box 70, Folder 28)
    - Statement of Originality Form, circa 1968-1974 (Box 70, Folder 29)
    - Stationary, 1968-1969; 1966 (Box 70, Folder 30)
    - Stolen Paintings, 1973-1974 (Box 70, Folder 31)
    - Studio Museum, 1980 (Box 70, Folder 32)
    - "T" Miscellaneous, 1968-1976 (Box 70, Folder 33-34)
    - Telephone, 1974-1975 (Box 70, Folder 35)
    - Tour (Summer 1970) (Box 70, Folder 36)
    - "U" Miscellaneous, 1968-1975 (Box 70, Folder 37)
    - Universities, 1968 (Box 70, Folder 38)
    - "V" Miscellaneous, 1971-1976 (Box 70, Folder 39-40)
    - "W" Miscellaneous, 1967-1981 (Box 70, Folder 41-42)
    - Weiss, T.F., 1968-1971 (Box 70, Folder 43)
    - "X-Z" Miscellaneous, 1968-1984 (Box 70, Folder 44-45)
  - Artist's Files, 1938-1983; 2.2
    Artist's files found here typically contain three types of materials: correspondence, public relations materials, and scrapbook pages. Scrapbook pages typically include photos of artwork and the artist, clippings, exhibition printed materials. Additional scrapbook pages for various artists are housed in subseries 2.5. Artists found here overlap with those in other series and subseries, and contain related materials. Researchers are encouraged to consult other series regarding particular artists.
    - Adams, James, 1977 (Box 71, Folder 1)
    - Adler, Lee, 1967-1976 (Box 71, Folder 2)
    - Albert, Calvin, 1973-1974 (Box 71, Folder 3)
    - Andrews, Oliver, 1969-1979; 1 Film reels Handwritten note on original container: 3 Waterblades Fullerton June 1971 I Oliver Andrews 16 mm (Box 71, Folder 4-11)
    - Aronson, David, 1960s-1979 (Box 71, Folder 12-19)
    - Aronson, David, 1960-circa 1975 (Box 72, Folder 1-5)
    - Backstrand, Jay, 1967-1970 (Box 72, Folder 6-8)
    - Battenberg, John, 1968 (Box 72, Folder 9)
    - Beasley, Bruce, circa 1962-1968 (Box 72, Folder 10-11)
    - Bechtle, Robert, 1960s-1973 (Box 72, Folder 12-14)
    - Bircheff, Philip, 1973 (Box 72, Folder 15)
    - Blitt, Rita, 1975-1977 (Box 72, Folder 16)
    - Borge, Ralph, 1967 (Box 72, Folder 17)
    - Butler, K.J., 1968-1974 (Box 72, Folder 18-21)
    - Carroll, Robert, 1960s (Box 72, Folder 22-24)
    - Chamberlain, Elwyn, circa 1961 (Box 72, Folder 25)
    - Chen Ting-shih, 1966-1968 (Box 72, Folder 26)
    - Chuang Che, 1966-1979 (Box 72, Folder 27-29)
    - Chuang Che, circa 1965-1974 (Box 73, Folder 1)
    - Colescott, Warrington, 1965-1983 (Box 73, Folder 2-5)
    - Collie, Alberto, 1963-1978 (Box 73, Folder 6-10)
    - Craggs, Michael, 1976-circa 1977 (Box 73, Folder 11)
    - Crawford, Ralston, 1945-1972 (Box 73, Folder 12-19)
    - D'Arista, Robert, 1965-1975 (Box 73, Folder 20-22)
    - D'Arista, Robert, 1955-1972 (Box 74, Folder 1-2)
    - Da Vinci, Leonardo, 1973-1974 (Box 74, Folder 3)
    - Fabert, Jacques, 1960s-1974 (Box 74, Folder 4-7)
    - Fifth Moon Group, 1966-1968; 1974 (Box 74, Folder 8)
    - Flynn, Robert, 1968-1970 (Box 74, Folder 9)
    - Fong Chung-ray, 1971-1977 (Box 74, Folder 10)
    - French, Stephen, 1968-1974 (Box 74, Folder 11-12)
    - Gallo, Samuel, 1969-1976 (Box 74, Folder 13)
    - Gatewood, Maud F., 1967-1968 (Box 74, Folder 14)
    - Gibran, Kahlil, circa 1961-1964 (Box 74, Folder 15)
    - Gikow, Ruth, 1950s-circa 1964 (Box 74, Folder 16-17)
    - Gooch, Gerald, 1966-1971 (Box 74, Folder 18-20)
    - Green, Anthony, 1967-1974 (Box 74, Folder 21-25)
    - Grippe, Peter, 1950s-1960s (Box 74, Folder 26-27)
    - Guglielmi, Louis, circa 1930s-1950s (Box 74, Folder 28)
    - Guglielmi, Louis, 1938-1960s (Box 75, Folder 1-4)
    - Hack, Howard, 1964-1969 (Box 75, Folder 5-7)
    - Haller, Arlene, 1977; 1975 (Box 75, Folder 8)
    - Han Hsiang Ning, 1966-1967 (Box 75, Folder 9)
    - Harman, Maryann, 1972-1973 (Box 75, Folder 10)
    - Harris, Conley, 1969 (Box 75, Folder 11)
    - Hasior, Wladyslaw, 1973 (Box 75, Folder 12)
    - Hebald, Milton, circa 1950s-1982 (Box 75, Folder 13-24)
    - Hebald, Milton, circa 1950s-1970 (Box 76, Folder 1-15)
    - Hebald, Milton, 1959-1971 (Box 77, Folder 1-4)
    - Hitchcock, Ray, 1976-1978 (Box 77, Folder 5)
    - Hollingsworth, A.C., circa 1970-1975 (Box 77, Folder 6-9)
    - Horiuchi, Paul, 1971 (Box 77, Folder 10)
    - Hyson, Jean, 1968-1973 (Box 77, Folder 11)
    - Johnson, Guy, 1958-1970 (Box 77, Folder 12-14)
    - Karwoski, Richard, 1974-1976 (Box 77, Folder 15)
    - Kearns, James, 1960s (Box 77, Folder 16)
    - Krewel, John, 1975-1978 (Box 77, Folder 17)
    - Lancaster, Edward, 1972-1979 (Box 77, Folder 18)
    - Laurentiu, Mihail, 1969-1970 (Box 77, Folder 19)
      Oversized material housed in Box 120, Folder 1
    - Lazzo, Constantine (Deno), 1975-1976 (Box 77, Folder 20)
    - Lebrun, Rico, circa 1950s-1981 (Box 77, Folder 21-29)
    - Lebrun, Rico, circa 1950s-1970s (Box 78, Folder 1-11)
    - Leitzes, John, 1972 (Box 78, Folder 12)
    - Levi, Julian, 1945-1965 (Box 78, Folder 13-15)
    - Levi, Julian, circa 1950s-1960s (Box 79, Folder 1-3)
    - Liu Kuo Sung, circa 1960s-1982 (Box 79, Folder 4-20)
    - Liu Kuo Sung, circa 1960s-1974 (Box 80, Folder 1-3)
    - Lomoe, Julie, 1968 (Box 80, Folder 4)
    - Lundin, Norman, circa 1968-1970 (Box 80, Folder 5-6)
    - Lurker, Ernest, 1969 (Box 80, Folder 7)
    - Meigs, Walter, 1960-1981 (Box 80, Folder 8-13)
    - Messing, Jack, circa 1960s (Box 80, Folder 14)
    - Milles, Carl, circa 1968-1970 (Box 80, Folder 15-16)
    - Millman, Edward, 1950s-1960s (Box 80, Folder 17-20)
    - Nichols, James, 1968-1974 (Box 80, Folder 21-23)
    - Ohaski, Yukata, 1968-1980 (Box 80, Folder 24-26)
    - Ossi, James, circa 1980 (Box 80, Folder 27)
    - Oxtoby, David, 1960s-1970 (Box 80, Folder 28-31)
      Oversized material housed in Box 120, Folder 2
    - Oxtoby, David, 1960s (Box 81, Folder 1)
    - Paterson, Anthony, 1976 (Box 81, Folder 2)
    - Pattison, Abbott, 1950s-1974 (Box 81, Folder 3-6)
    - Penthouse Gallery (San Francisco), 1964-1965 (Box 81, Folder 7)
    - Pereira, Irene Rice, 1950s-1960s (Box 81, Folder 8-11)
    - Prestopino, Gregorio, 1950-1960s (Box 81, Folder 12-17)
    - Procktor, Patrick, 1965-1974 (Box 81, Folder 18-21)
    - Rahir, Claude, 1971-1972 (Box 82, Folder 1)
    - Rembrandt, 1973 (Box 82, Folder 2)
    - Richardson, Sam, 1968 (Box 82, Folder 3)
    - Scholder, Fritz, 1966-1972 (Box 82, Folder 4-6)
    - Schuler, Melvin, 1968-1969 (Box 82, Folder 7)
    - Sindelir, Robert J. [Sindelir Gallery, Florida], 1969 (Box 82, Folder 8)
    - Siporin, Mitchell, 1942-1960s (Box 82, Folder 9-10)
    - Spafford, Michael, circa 1967-1970 (Box 82, Folder 11-13)
    - Spratt, Fred, 1968-1969 (Box 82, Folder 14)
    - Squeri, Robert, 1969-1975 (Box 82, Folder 15)
    - Sumers, Martin, 1977 (Box 82, Folder 16)
    - Thompson, Paul, 1967-1968 (Box 82, Folder 17)
    - Tift, Mary, circa 1968-1969 (Box 82, Folder 18-19)
    - Valentine, DeWain, circa 1968-1971 (Box 82, Folder 20-21)
    - Varming, Erik, circa 1967-1970 (Box 82, Folder 22-23)
    - Vaughan, Michael, circa 1968-1969 (Box 82, Folder 24-25)
    - Wakhovitch, Alexandre, 1969 (Box 82, Folder 26)
    - Wall, James, 1976 (Box 82, Folder 27)
    - Walmsley, William, 1968-1972 (Box 82, Folder 28)
    - Washington, James, Jr., 1962-1975; 1984-1985 (Box 82, Folder 29-32)
    - Weege, William, 1968-1969 (Box 82, Folder 33)
    - Whistler, James McNeil, circa 1960s (Box 82, Folder 34-35)
    - White, Jack, 1969-1972 (Box 82, Folder 36)
    - Wilde, John, 1971-1973 (Box 82, Folder 37-38)
    - Wilkins, Tim, 1975 (Box 82, Folder 39)
    - Williams, Hiram, 1966-1969 (Box 82, Folder 40-43)
    - Wong, Wucius, circa 1970s (Box 83, Folder 1-2)
    - Wright, G. Alan, 1960s-1970s (Box 83, Folder 3-4)
    - Zerbe, Karl, 1950s-1970s (Box 83, Folder 5-15)
      (Includes index cards housed in Box 84, shoebox 1)
    - Various Artists, Biographical Information, 1958-1971 (Box 83, Folder 16-21)
    - Various Artists, Correspondence, 1966-1974 (Box 84, Folder 1-4)
    - Various Artists, "M", circa 1960s-1970s (Box 84, Folder 5)
    - Oversized, Mihail Laurentiu, circa late 1960s (Box 120, Folder 1)
      Oversized material from Box 77, Folder 19
    - Oversized, David Oxtoby, circa 1960s-1970s (Box 120, Folder 2)
      Oversized material from Box 80, Folder 28
  - Business Records, circa 1960s-1970s; 2.3
    This small subseries includes one folder of corporation records and index cards for collectors and artists.
    - Artist's Addresses, circa 1960s-1970s (Box 84, Folder 6)
      Index cards housed in Box 84, shoebox 1
    - Collectors, circa 1960s-1970s (Box 84, Folder 7)
      Index cards housed in Box 84, shoebox 2
    - Corporate Records, 1966-1967 (Box 84, Folder 8)
  - Financial and Sales Records, circa 1958-1985; 2.4
    Found are disassembled accounting ledgers, artist's statements, bank statements, check stubs, consignment sheets, paid bills, sales invoices, index cards for sold artwork, and tax records.
    - Artist's Artwork Inventory, circa 1966-1974 (Box 84, Folder 9)
    - Artist's Commissions, 1968-1970 (Box 84, Folder 10)
    - Artist's Statements, 1968-1969 (Box 84, Folder 11-12)
    - Bank Statements, Chemical Bank, 1966-1967 (Box 84, Folder 13-14)
    - Bank Statements, Chemical Bank, 1967-1969 (Box 85, Folder 1-12)
    - Bank Statements, Chemical Bank, 1969-1970; 1981-1983 (Box 86, Folder 1-9)
    - Cash Receipts and Disbuursements, 1966-1967 (Box 86, Folder 10)
    - Cashbook, 1970-1981 (Box 86, Folder 11-12)
    - Check Stubs, 1966-1969 (Box 86, Folder 13-16)
    - Check Stubs, 1969 (Box 87, Folder 1)
    - Commissions Payable Due From Artist, 1967-1972 (Box 87, Folder 2)
    - Consignment Sheets, 1968-1977 (Box 87, Folder 3-11)
      Oversized materials housed in Box 120, Folder 3
    - Consignment Sheets, Via Bill Wallace, 1969-1970 (Box 87, Folder 12)
    - Deposit Slips, 1970 (Box 87, Folder 13)
    - Loose Checks Unfiled, 1967-1969 (Box 87, Folder 14)
    - Paid Accounts Receivable, 1966-1970 (Box 87, Folder 15-19)
    - Paid Accounts Receivable, 1967-1970 (Box 88, Folder 1)
    - Paid Bills (1968), 1966-1969 (Box 88, Folder 2-9)
    - Paid Bills (1970), 1969-1970 (Box 88, Folder 10-13)
    - Paid Bills [1971-1973], 1970-1973 (Box 88, Folder 14-18)
    - Paid Bills [1971-1973], 1970-1973 (Box 89, Folder 1-2)
    - Paid Bills, 1982 (Box 89, Folder 3)
    - Petty Cash, 1964-1973 (Box 89, Folder 4-9)
    - Purchase Journal, 1968-1970 (Box 89, Folder 10-11)
    - Sales Invoices, 1968-1986 (Box 89, Folder 12-20)
    - Sold Cards (3 shoeboxes), circa 1958-1970s (Box 90, Folder 1-3)
    - Tax Correspondence With IRS, 1971; 1981-1982 (Box 91, Folder 1)
    - Tax Records, 1981-1985 (Box 91, Folder 2-4)
    - Unpaid Bills, Early Years, 1969-1970 (Box 91, Folder 5)
    - Year End Figures, 1971-1982 (Box 91, Folder 6)
    - Oversized Binder Covers, Consignment Sheets, 1971-1972 (Box 120, Folder 3)
      Oversized materials from Box 87, Folders 9-10
  - Scrapbooks, 1951-1970s; 2.5
    Artist scrapbooks are arranged first alphabetically by last name, followed by the exhibition scrapbooks, arranged chronologically.
    Found are scrapbooks for artists and scrapbooks for exhibition seasons 1966-1974. Materials found in scrapbooks include black and white photographs of artwork, clippings, printed materials, and price lists. Additional scrapbook pages for various artists are housed in subseries 2.2. The exhibition scrapbooks found here are related to those found in subseries 1.9.
    - Artists (Adler-Breed), 1964-circa 1974 (Box 91, Folder 7)
    - Artists (Calligraphers-Dove), 1960s (Box 91, Folder 8)
    - Artists (Flynn-Frisch), 1960s-circa 1974 (Box 91, Folder 9)
    - Artists (Gallo-Guglielmi), 1959-circa 1974 (Box 91, Folder 10)
    - Artists (Grippe-Gikow), 1960s (Box 91, Folder 11)
    - Artists (Hans-Hirsche), 1960s (Box 91, Folder 12)
    - Artists (Holbrook-Hyson), 1960s-circa 1971 (Box 91, Folder 13)
    - Artists (James-Kuniyoshi), 1960s-1971 (Box 91, Folder 14)
    - Artists (Lardera-Lennard), 1960s-1972 (Box 91, Folder 15)
      Oversized material housed in Box 120, Folder 4
    - Artists (Liautaud-Moll), 1960s-1970s (Box 91, Folder 16)
    - Artists (Nakamura-Peipert), 1960s-1972 (Box 91, Folder 17)
    - Artists (Pereira-Schneider), 1951-1973 (Box 91, Folder 18)
    - Artists (Selby-Sironi), 1960s-1974 (Box 91, Folder 19)
    - Artists (Spencer-Sumers), 1959-1970s (Box 92, Folder 1)
    - Artists (Tobey-Vaughn), 1960s-1970s (Box 92, Folder 2)
    - Artists (Weber-Zerdman), 1960s-1972 (Box 92, Folder 3)
    - Artists (Zerdman), circa 1960s-1972 (Box 92, Folder 4)
    - Artists, Miscellaneous Scrapbook Pages, 1962-1971 (Box 92, Folder 5)
    - Exhibitions (Books 9-15), 1966-1974 (Box 92, Folder 6-16)
    - Exhibitions (Book 15), 1973-1974 (Box 93, Folder 1)
    - Oversized, Berto Lardera and his Sculpture at Wingspread, circa 1970s (Box 120, Folder 4)
      Oversized material from Box 90, Folder 15
- Forms & Objects, Inc., circa 1959-1984; circa 1931; Series 3; 13.5 Linear feet Boxes 93-106, 120
  Forms & Objects, Inc. is documented through correspondence with artists, lecture notes, public relations materials, business records, financial and sales records, scrapbooks and photographic materials.
  This series is arranged as 7 subseries:
  3.1: Correspondence, circa 1959-1984
  3.2: Lectures, 1971-1973
  3.3: Public Relations Files, 1964-1971
  3.4: Business Records, 1960s-1970s
  3.5: Financial and Sales Records, 1968-1983
  3.6: Scrapbooks, circa 1931, 1960s-1970s
  3.7: Photographic Materials, circa 1960s-1970s
  - Correspondence, circa 1959-1984; 3.1
    This subseries contains mostly incoming and outgoing correspondence with or related to artists, interfiled with scattered price lists, printed materials, photographic and other materials. Also found is some correspondence related to exhibitions, form letters, scattered inventory records, insurance and other general business records.
    Folders are arranged alphabetically by folder title, which may be correspondent's last name or subject.
    - "A" Miscellaneous Craftsmen, circa 1959-1980 (Box 93, Folder 2)
    - "A-C" Miscellaneous, 1969-1971 (Box 93, Folder 3)
    - American Crafts Council, 1971-1984 (Box 93, Folder 4)
    - American Greeting Card Gallery Exhibit [Arts/Objects], 1973 (Box 93, Folder 5)
    - Apple Pin, 1975-1976 (Box 93, Folder 6)
    - Appleton, Rachel, 1968-1971 (Box 93, Folder 7)
    - Appraisals, 1969-1981 (Box 93, Folder 8)
    - Arneson, Robert, 1968-1974 (Box 93, Folder 9)
    - "B" Miscellaneous Craftsmen, 1968-1980 (Box 93, Folder 10)
    - Bailey, Clayton, 1967-1974 (Box 93, Folder 11)
    - Barron, Mark, circa 1968-1974 (Box 93, Folder 12)
    - Bauer, Fred, Dorpat Book, 1969-1972 (Box 93, Folder 13)
    - Billeci, Andre [Arts/Objects?], 1972-1973 (Box 93, Folder 14)
    - Blair Printing, 1970-1971 (Box 93, Folder 15)
    - Bondi, Stephen, 1973-1974 (Box 93, Folder 16)
    - Buonagurio, Toby, 1973 (Box 93, Folder 17)
    - Brynner, Irena, 1971-1977 (Box 93, Folder 18)
    - Brynner, Irena and Jacob Weinstein, 1972-1977 (Box 93, Folder 19)
    - Burglery, 1970-1973 (Box 93, Folder 20)
    - Burglery (November 22, 1973), 1978; 1972-1974 (Box 93, Folder 21)
    - "C" Miscellaneous Craftsmen, 1968-1984 (Box 93, Folder 22-23)
    - Cartwright, Roy, 1968-1974 (Box 93, Folder 24)
    - Castle, Wendell, 1966-1973 (Box 93, Folder 25-26)
    - Charities, Gifts and Donations, 1968-1976; 1983 (Box 93, Folder 27)
    - Chemical Bank, 1982; 1977 (Box 93, Folder 28)
    - Chihuly, Dale, 1968-1974 (Box 93, Folder 29)
    - Christman, Anne Hornby, 1968-1969 (Box 93, Folder 30)
    - Commissions, Possible, 1970 (Box 93, Folder 31)
    - Con Edison, 1968-1975 (Box 93, Folder 32)
    - Consigned Works by Various Owners, 1970-1971 (Box 93, Folder 33)
    - Cooper-Hewitt Craft Fair, 1979-1981 (Box 93, Folder 34-35)
    - Craft Horizons, 1977-1982 (Box 94, Folder 1)
    - "D" Miscellaneous Craftsmen, 1968-1973 (Box 94, Folder 2)
    - "D-F" Miscellaneous, 1968-1981 (Box 94, Folder 3)
    - da Swart, Jan, 1963; 1969 (Box 94, Folder 4)
    - Daniels, Martha, 1976 (Box 94, Folder 5)
    - Di Mare, Dominic, 1968-1970 (Box 94, Folder 6)
    - Display Materials, circa 1968 (Box 94, Folder 7)
    - Dreisback, Fritz, 1972-1975 (Box 94, Folder 8)
    - Duncan, Tom, 1973-1974 (Box 94, Folder 9)
    - Dunning Letters, 1969 (Box 94, Folder 10)
    - "E" Miscellaneous Craftsmen, 1968-1978 (Box 94, Folder 11)
    - Earl, Jack [brochures], circa 1973 (Box 94, Folder 12)
    - Espenet, Arthur Carpenter, 1968-1974 (Box 94, Folder 13)
    - Everson Museum of Art, 1968-1970 (Box 94, Folder 14)
    - Exhibitions
      - Enamel Group Show, 1969 (Box 94, Folder 15)
      - "Animals in Contemporary Art" (August 4-31, 1969) (Box 94, Folder 16)
      - Ceiling Show, 1968-1969 (Box 94, Folder 17)
      - Fountain Show, 1968-1969 (Box 94, Folder 18)
      - Miscellaneous, 1969 (Box 94, Folder 19)
      - "For Men Only", 1971 (Box 94, Folder 20-21)
      - "Glass Show '73", 1972-1973 (Box 94, Folder 22)
    - "F" Miscellaneous Craftsmen, 1968-1981 (Box 94, Folder 23)
    - Fisch, Arline, 1968-1977 (Box 94, Folder 24-25)
    - Fishback, Kurt, 1975 (Box 94, Folder 26)
    - Fleming, Frank, 1976 (Box 94, Folder 27)
    - Freeslate International, 1968-1970 (Box 94, Folder 28)
    - Friends of the Craft, Inc. (Gallery), 1974-1975 (Box 94, Folder 29)
    - Furman, David, 1969-1978 (Box 94, Folder 30)
    - "G" Miscellaneous Craftsmen, 1969-1975 (Box 94, Folder 31)
    - "G-I" Miscellaneous, 1968-1977 (Box 94, Folder 32)
    - Gad, Simone, 1973-1977 (Box 94, Folder 33)
    - Gilhooly, David, 1971-1978 (Box 94, Folder 34)
    - Ginsberg, Elizabet, circa 1972 (Box 94, Folder 35)
    - Girls Club of Manhattan, 1970-1971 (Box 94, Folder 36)
    - Gregory, Waylande, 1978-1981 (Box 94, Folder 37)
    - Gregory, Waylande, Estate Inventory, circa 1974 (Box 94, Folder 38-39)
    - Gregory, Waylande, Robert Buff (Attorney), 1980 (Box 94, Folder 40)
    - Gregory, Yolande, Contracts, 1973-1980 (Box 94, Folder 41-42)
    - Gregory, Yolande, Kansas, 1976-1981 (Box 94, Folder 43)
    - Gregory, Yolande, Will, 1976 (Box 94, Folder 44)
    - Gronborg, Erik, 1968-1972 (Box 94, Folder 45)
    - Guermonprez, Trudi, 1968-1971 (Box 94, Folder 46)
    - "H" Miscellaneous Craftsmen, 1968-1979 (Box 94, Folder 47)
    - Halem, Henry, 1968-1969 (Box 95, Folder 1)
    - Halem, Judi Meyers, 1969-1974 (Box 95, Folder 2)
    - Hallman, Ted, 1968-1969 (Box 95, Folder 3)
    - Hanes Dye and Finishing Co., 1968-1969 (Box 95, Folder 4)
    - Harris, Peter, 1971 (Box 95, Folder 5)
    - Heaton, Maurice, 1968-1970 (Box 95, Folder 6)
    - Helfant, Nancy, 1975-1979 (Box 95, Folder 7)
    - Helwig, Harold B., 1968-1973 (Box 95, Folder 8)
    - Hui Ka-Kwong, 1968-1972 (Box 95, Folder 9)
    - Hultberg, Paul, 1968-1974 (Box 95, Folder 10)
    - "I" Miscellaneous Craftsmen, 1970-1974 (Box 95, Folder 11)
    - Insurance Claims, 1968-1970 (Box 95, Folder 12-13)
    - "J" Miscellaneous Craftsmen, 1968-1979 (Box 95, Folder 14)
    - "J-L" Miscellaneous, 1968-1974 (Box 95, Folder 15)
    - Jewish Organizations, 1969 (Box 95, Folder 16)
    - Johnson, Gilbert C., 1972-1976 (Box 95, Folder 17)
    - Jurying, 1970-1974 (Box 95, Folder 18)
    - Jurying Completed, 1969; 1974-1982 (Box 95, Folder 19)
    - "K" Miscellaneous Craftsmen, 1968-1981 (Box 95, Folder 20)
    - Kaufman, Glen, 1968-1972 (Box 95, Folder 21)
    - Keyser, Bill, 1972-1974 (Box 95, Folder 22-23)
    - Kington, Brent, 1968-1972 (Box 95, Folder 24-25)